http://shopriogrande.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
At ShopCity.com, Inc., the protection of your personal information is always a top priority. Our Policy regarding the collection,
use and disclosure, if any, of personal information can be broken down
into the 10 principles covered in the Personal Information
Protection and Electronic Documents Act ("PIPEDA"). See Personal Information for a list of the types of personal information which we collect from you subject to this Policy when you do business with us.
AccountabilityShopCity.com, Inc. is responsible for personal information under its control.We have designated a Privacy Officer who is accountable for our compliance with this Policy and all applicable privacy laws.All ShopCity.com, Inc. employees are responsible for day-to-day compliance.When
we use trusted third parties to act on our behalf by performing such
functions as fulfilling orders, delivering packages, processing credit
card payments or providing customer service, contractual or other
appropriate means are used to ensure compliance by such third parties
with this Policy and all applicable privacy laws.
Identifying PurposesUnless the
purpose is self-evident due to the nature of the transaction in
question, ShopCity.com, Inc. will identify the purposes for which
personal information is collected at or before the time the information
is collected.The proposed purposes will be described in a reasonably understandable manner.An
example of a self-evident purpose is requesting the name and address of
the person placing an order in order to ensure proper delivery.
ConsentWe will collect, use or
disclose your personal information only with your knowledge and
consent, except where required or permitted by law.ShopCity.com, Inc. will not make your consent a requirement to the supply of
a product or a service other than required to be able to supply the
product or service.Consent can be express or, in some
circumstances, implied, and given in writing, by using or not using a
check-off box, electronically, orally (in person or by telephone), or
by your conduct, such as use of a product or service.In
determining the type of consent to obtain, ShopCity.com, Inc. will
consider all relevant factors, including the sensitivity of the
information and your reasonable expectations.You may withdraw
your consent at any time, on reasonable notice, subject to legal or
contractual restrictions. ShopCity.com, Inc. will inform you of the
implications of doing so.
Limiting CollectionThe collection of
personal information by ShopCity.com, Inc. will be limited to what is
necessary for the purposes which it identifies.We will collect personal information by fair and lawful means.
Limiting Use, Disclosure, and RetentionPersonal
information will not be used or disclosed for purposes other than those
for which it was collected, except with your consent or as required or
permitted by law.It will be retained only as long as necessary for these purposes or as required by law.
Accuracy, Integrity & AttributionShopCity.com’s mission is to have the relevant local business
information.  All of the information on our sites is either directly
attributed to the business owner or a person working on their behalf,
or by importing databases of publicly available information in
accordance with the law.
We strive to keep information as accurate, complete and up-to-date as
necessary for the purposes for which it is to be used.  If you find
that any information on the ShopCity.com network of sites is inaccurate
or out-of-date, please contact us via email at mistakes@shopcity.com
or
by accessing the 'Report Mistake' form located at the right side of every
business listing.
If you wish to have your personal information deleted, please let us
know in the same manner as referred to above.  We will process these
requests as quickly as possible while also ensuring the accuracy of claims submitted.
SafeguardsShopCity.com, Inc. will
protect personal information by security safeguards appropriate to the
sensitivity of the information, including through the use of the
following measures: physical (e.g., locked filing cabinets, restricted
access, appropriate disposal of personal information), organizational
(e.g., security clearances, access only on a "need to know" basis),
technological (e.g., passwords, encryption) and training of employees.
See Technology and Security.
OpennessInformation about our
policies and practices relating to the management of personal
information will be made readily available to individuals.
Individual AccessUpon request, ShopCity.com, Inc. will inform you of the existence, use and disclosure of
personal information relating to you, and give you access to that
information. You have the right to challenge the accuracy and
completeness of your information and have it amended as appropriate.However,
in certain circumstances permitted by law, this information will not be
disclosed to you. Some examples of these circumstances are information
that contains references to other individuals, that cannot be disclosed
for legal, security or commercial proprietary reasons, or that is
subject to solicitor-client or litigation privilege.
Contacting us and/or Challenging ComplianceFor
anything to do with this Policy, including questions or comments, or to
challenge our compliance with this Policy, please contact us as follows:Thomas LeClair, Privacy OfficerShopCity.com, Inc.270 King Street
Midland, Ontario, CanadaL4R 3M5email: privacy@shopcity.com
ShopCity.com, Inc. will inform individuals who make enquiries or
lodge complaints about its enquiry or complaint procedures, as
applicable. If a complaint is found to be justified, we will take
appropriate measures, including, if necessary, amending our policies
and practices.
Of course, this Policy is subject to PIPEDA and/or any other
applicable privacy laws and ShopCity.com, Inc.'s right to change it at
any time.
Personal Information We Collect
ShopCity.com, Inc. asks for your name, address, email address, and
other personal information when you create an account online. You will
also be asked for personal information when you make an online
purchase, or enter into contests or promotions. This information is
used to process your orders and to allow us to communicate with you.
The information also enables ShopCity.com, Inc. to customize products or
services to better meet your preferences and to offer you products and
services from ShopCity.com, Inc. that may be of interest to you.
To process and/or fulfill your order, trusted third parties may be
used to perfom the required function, and in such cases, appropriate
personal information will be given to them to allow for the service to
be provided. Contractual or other appropriate means would always be
used to ensure third party compliance with our privacy policy and all
applicable privacy laws.
